[{"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Rudy, how are you?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "Well, I'm good, but I don't know what to make of all of this.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "There's -- there really isn't a legal defense, there's an emotional defense.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Do you think there is a reasonable defense for putting into the public domain the material that he reasonably judiciously chose to put out there?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "You can try all that.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Is there a public interest defense?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, I think the president is doing everything he can to bring him to justice.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "Is there any more that the president should be doing to try and bring him to justice?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "I think we would.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "-- for political gain and perhaps even intelligence?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "I think it's pretty extraordinary that anybody who would call themself a journalist would publicly muse about whether or not other journalists should be charged with felonies.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "To the extent that you have aided and abetted Snowden, even in his current movements, why shouldn't you, Mr. Greenwald, be charged with a crime?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Well, I mean I think a journalist has the power and the right to ask any question that they want.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Or should we just be focusing on Snowden himself?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, if I were George Zimmerman, I would be furious at my lawyer unless the lawyer told him he was going to open with that joke.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What did you make of it?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "The joke was inappropriate and wasn't funny.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "What was your reaction today to day one of this eagerly awaited Zimmerman- Trayvon trial today?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I think it's hard to avoid race in this trial.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Do you think that will sustain itself through the trial, or do you think inevitably it will turn into a race trial?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "You know, honestly, I haven't followed the case as much as others have.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Are you in the hero or villain camp?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I care tremendously.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "How much do you care about your own private data being made available to a government?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "I think that we all grow, we all develop.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Nobody wants to make a decision?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I'm not so sure it is.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Is it an overreaction?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I agree with you.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Everything changes, but are you growing?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Well, I'm no Fidel Castro - (LAUGHTER)", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "How long could you talk for if you wanted?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Well, the first sign which both of these cast members had, was shortness of breath.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "For anybody who is looking for this, who worried about it, you know, maybe has heart issues and so on, what should they be really, really looking for?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "It's a risk factor for heart problems because it can damage the heart while you're taking the cocaine or doing some of these other drugs or alcohol.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Does that have a material impact on later heart issues?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "It is genetic, but it's only a third genetic.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Is it genetic at all, this kind of -- this kind of heart attack?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "You cannot get the flu from the flu shot because the material is actually dead flu virus.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "The myth about these, and I'm told there's a myth, is that you can actually get flu or flu-like symptoms simply by having the shot, is that true?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "That's a myth.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "That is a myth?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "It's exactly what happened.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Does that make sense to you?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, Piers.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Can you at least just say, \"Sorry, Piers\"?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Well, it's an interesting perspective.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Where do you sit with this?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Well, if you can keep your weight down within a reasonable amount as you get pregnant, it makes life a lot easier for you and the baby.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Can you talk about what's been going on there for women who are watching who are curious?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Anything, and other systems, too.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "And this can be used with any game like \"Call of Duty,\" any of the popular games?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Is it working?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "How is that not to a disturbed mind -- and this is a sniper rifle you have, right?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "I think the argument -- the least effective argument I've heard about guns is -- especially with the AR-15s which these replicate, is they're just good fun.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "I mean, and you know, would you take that away from them, the joy of just having a little fun inside their house?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "No, but I'm not mentally disturbed.", "docId": "130624pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Well, when you were holding that sniper rifle, did you feel like shooting someone?", "qSentId": 669}]